[
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /chatter_xta?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /chatter_xvb?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called listener_xbl?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called listener_xkv?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called talker_xoa?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called talker?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is talker? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called listener?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is listener? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a ROS2 entity called /chatter?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 0,
    "category": "ENTITY",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "question": "What kind of ROS2 entity is /chatter? Possible answers: 1- ROS topic, 2- ROS service, 3- ROS node.",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node talker publish to topic /chatter?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node talker subscribed to topic /chatter?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics can node talker publish?",
    "answer": "/chatter"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics is node talker subscribed?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Does node listener publish to topic /chatter?",
    "answer": "No"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is node listener subscribed to topic /chatter?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "PUBLISH",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics can node listener publish?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SUBSCRIBE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "To which topics is node listener subscribed?",
    "answer": "/chatter"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node talker provide?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node talker use as a client?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "SERVICE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node listener provide?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "CLIENT",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "Which services does node listener use as a client?",
    "answer": "None"
  },
  {
    "level": 1,
    "category": "TOPIC_TYPE",
    "type": "OPEN",
    "question": "What is the type of topic /chatter?",
    "answer": "std_msgs/msg/String"
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "category": "MESSAGE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a communication path from node talker to node listener via a topic or service?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "category": "MESSAGE",
    "type": "BOOL",
    "question": "Is there a communication path from node listener to node talker via a topic or service?",
    "answer": "No"
  }
]